Finding Aid for Inter-Cooperative Council (Ann Arbor, Mich.) records, 1932-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Organizational Topical files
  - History, House chronology circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - History, Names of houses (Box 45)
  - History project administrative materials 1990-1992 (Box 45)
  - History projects, "Archiving Overview" (Box 45)
  - House budgets 1951-1975 (Box 45)
  - House plaques
    - General information for wall plaques (Box 45)
    - Nakamura wall plaque materials 1995-1996 (Box 45)
    - Osterweil wall plaque materials 1994-1996 (Box 45)
    - Owen wall plaque materials (photograph of Robert Owen statue) (Box 45)
  - Information on grants and funding (Box 45)
  - Informational and introductory material (Box 45)
  - Intercooperative Purchasing Fund
    - Mixed materials 1940-1968, 1978, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Financial records 1949-1969 (Box 45)
  - ICC Stewards' Co-op, Ledger 1978-1980 (Box 45)
  - Intern program: Background/History (Box 45)
  - Interns 1987-2010, 6 folders (Box 45)
  - Interview excerpts (Box 45)
  - Jerry Cohen Foundation, Correspondence and information packets 1998 (Box 45)
  - Labadie Collection, Donations information and correspondence 1995-2004 (Box 45)
  - Library
    - Mixed materials, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Agreement for ownership of the Art Danforth Library 2009 (Box 45)
    - List of collection donors to the Art Danforth Library circa 2011 (Box 45)
  - List of Co-ops by Ann Arbor named subdivisions (Box 45)
  - Maintenance materials (Box 45)
  - Manager's reports 1947-1948 (Box 45)
  - Manuals (various) (Box 45)
  - Member/alumni news and correspondence
    - Holiday letters and news clippings 1997-2003 (Box 45)
    - Clippings and correspondence 1966-1985 (Box 45)
    - Clippings and correspondence 1961-2011, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Membership Committee manual (Box 21)
  - Membership profile / surveys (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Articles, essays, event announcements, correspondence and notes 1966-2000 (Box 21)
    - Concept paper, essay, background information, etc. (Box 21)
    - Clippings, correspondence, and event announcements 1987 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence, financial records, and other materials 1942-1979 (Box 21)
    - Food policies and procedures (Box 21)
    - Food-related materials 1970s, 1980s (Box 21)
    - General (Box 21)
    - Notes, clippings, reports, and correspondence 1955-1979 (Box 21)
    - Studies, reports, and articles 1947-1976 (Box 21)
    - Written materials on coops, conference programs (e.g., Central League of Coops) 1940s (Box 21)
  - Nakamura, John biography 1994 (Box 21)
  - New member introductory information (Box 21)
  - North Campus development (proposed) 1987 (Box 21)
  - Office reports 1994-1996 (Box 21)
  - Owner's manuals / members handbooks, 1970- circa 1988, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Planning, e.g. 5-year planning session, long-range planning retreat, etc. (Box 21)
  - Political and social issues (memorandum about) 1940s (Box 21)
  - Politics and political action materials 1936-1964 (Box 21)
  - Presidents lists (Box 46)
  - Presidents training material (Box 46)
  - "Quantity Recipes for Mass Food Service," 1952 (Box 46)
  - Quotes culled by Jim Jones (Box 46)
  - Report, Cooperative study program 1942 (Box 46)
  - Santa Cruz Co-op Assist Project 1996 (Box 46)
  - Scholarships, minutes and reports (Box 46)
  - Scholarships -- Leuchtman fund (Box 46)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy Committee (SHPC)/Resource Team (SHRT) (Box 46)
    - Historical development 1988-1998, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Correspondence, meeting agendas, and other materials 1998-2009, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Singham, A.W. (Box 46)
  - Slide shows and video productions
    - History presentation and slide scripts 1992, 1994 (Box 46)
    - History video script 1994 (Box 46)
    - Slide program for orientation 1993 (Box 46)
    - Video tape and slide show scripts/notes (Box 46)
  - Social Committee notebook (Box 46)
  - Staff reports 1985-1990, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Structural reorganization 1969 (Box 46)
  - Student Co-op Conference 1965 (Box 46)
  - Student Government Council/Michigan Student Assembly materials, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Student papers
    - Duquette, Kathy J.: "The Historic Houses of the Inter Cooperative Council at the University of Michigan," 1999 (Box 46)
    - Erdstein, Rachel: "Shared Values, Shared Lives," 1993 (Box 46)
    - Kingsbury, Judith: "'Ni neart go curle cheile': No Strength Without Combination," 1990 (Box 46)
    - May, Beverly: "A History of the Development of North American Housing Cooperatives," 1993 (Box 46)
    - Prathikanti, Sudha, "In my group's examination of cooperative...," circa 1980 (Box 46)
    - Walters, Debra: "Nakamura: Twenty-Five Years a Co-op," 1973 (Box 46)
  - Study, "The Leaders and Process of Decision-Making in a Student Cooperative," 1958 (Box 46)
  - University of Michigan Campus Safety Committee minutes 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Visitors
    - Australian Housing Co-ops, Wettenhall July 1985 (Box 46)
    - Mario Patera September 1985, June 1991 (Box 46)
    - International Trainees from the Cooperative Education and Management Seminar (University of Wisconsin) October 1985 (Box 46)
    - Ann Evans September 1987 (Box 46)
    - John Gauci (NCBA) June 7-8, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Swedish delegation August 18, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Habonim Dror 1992, 1993, 1994 (Box 46)
    - Otterbein College May 14, 2010 (Box 46)
  - Wilcox, Donald: "Even the Rocks Sang to Us: A contrapuntal drama of student life in a co-op in the 1950s" circa 2005 (Box 46)
- Correspondence Files
  The Correspondence Files series(1970s-1990s) consists of correspondence with individuals relating to the ICC, mainly alumni. The letters often contain personal reminiscences of life in the co-op houses. Much of the correspondence dates from the early and mid-1990s and is related to the research and publication of In our Own Hands.
  - Albright, Lyle (Box 47)
  - Ansteth, Bruce (Box 47)
  - Berlow, Ruth (Box 47)
  - Bissell, Silas Trim (Box 47)
  - Blumenthal, Werner (Box 47)
  - Bowne, Dorothy (Morris) (Box 47)
  - Buchele, Luther and Joan (Box 47)
  - Buntaine, Raymond E. (Box 47)
  - Carstensen, Patricia (Box 47)
  - Clyde, Ensign (Box 47)
  - Cohen, Zeldon (Box 47)
  - Cook, John R. (Box 47)
  - Cote, Louis J. (Box 47)
  - Cox, Robert (Box 47)
  - Davis, Bob (Box 47)
  - DeMarkey, David L. (Box 47)
  - Domar, Evsey (Box 47)
  - Dykstra, Fred (Box 47)
  - Dykstra, Joanne (Stoller) (Box 47)
  - Ehlers, Harold L. (Box 47)
  - Engelberg, Daniel (Box 47)
  - Epstein, Herman T. (Box 47)
  - Epstein, Marvin M. (Box 47)
  - Farmer, Bob (Box 47)
  - Field, Everett J. (Box 47)
  - Fuller, Judy (Hurwitz) (Box 47)
  - Furnier, Glenn (Box 47)
  - Gerstell, Frederick (Box 47)
  - Goldstein, Margaret (Box 47)
  - Grush, Erik (Box 47)
  - Hahn, Bill (Box 47)
  - Hanau, Richard (Box 47)
  - Haney, Alice J. (Box 47)
  - Hartung, Louise (Box 47)
  - Hathaway, Mary (Stevens) (Box 47)
    (daughter of A. K. Stevens)
  - Herzberg, Nancy (Box 47)
  - Hilberry, John D. "Jack" (Box 47)
  - Hilton, Robert (Box 47)
  - Holmes, Wilbur (Box 47)
  - Hubers, Paul (Box 47)
  - Hulack, Lawrence B. (Box 47)
  - Jarecki, Henry G. (Box 47)
  - Joseph, Richard K. (Box 47)
  - Kaczynski, Theodore (information only, no correspondence) (Box 47)
  - Keeton, Elvin E. (Box 47)
  - Kelley, Ruth (Bluck) (Box 47)
  - King, Jean Ledwith (Box 47)
  - Kira, George (Box 47)
  - Kresin, Cal (Box 47)
  - Lamb, Margaret (Box 47)
  - Lambrecht, Donald G. (Box 47)
  - Laschever, Barnett "Barney" (Box 47)
  - Lawrence, Jill (Box 47)
  - Lipsett, Lawrence (Box 47)
  - Malin, Herbert (Box 47)
  - Martin, Tom (Box 47)
  - McFerran, Warren A. (Box 47)
  - Melbin, Murray (Box 47)
  - Menonne, Doris Edwards (Box 47)
  - Miller, Sherwood P. (Box 47)
  - Moskowitz, Merwin (Box 47)
  - Nakamura, Frank (Box 47)
  - Newman, George F. (Box 47)
  - O'Connell, James (Box 47)
  - Olshansky, Don and Miriam Zahler-Olshansky (Box 47)
  - Orr, Charles (Box 47)
  - Peach, Robert (Box 47)
  - Pickerill, H. L. and Katheryn (Box 47)
  - Rees, Gerald "Jerry" (Box 47)
  - Rotkin, Esther (Repps) (Box 47)
  - Ruymaker, Ethel Shirwindt (Box 47)
  - Saltman, William M. (Box 47)
  - Sandberg, Bob (Box 47)
  - Sandifer, Caleb B. (Box 47)
  - Schulkin, Florence Pachter (Box 47)
  - Sendrow, Marvin (Box 47)
  - Shackman, Grace (Drob) (Box 47)
  - Shuey, Richard L. (Box 47)
  - Shugart, Robert (Box 47)
  - Smith, David Lyle (Box 47)
  - Solomon, Robert (Box 47)
  - Stein, Johanna (Kranold) (Box 47)
  - Sternlight, Lee (Frane) (Box 47)
  - Straus-Koch, Audrey (Box 47)
  - Strawn, Robertson (Box 47)
  - Travis, Jeff (Box 47)
  - Twork, Elton C. (Box 47)
  - VanDore, Bill (MacLeod) (Box 47)
  - Walden, Miriam Ellard (Box 47)
- Collected Research Materials
  The Collected Research materials series (1940s-1990s) consist of drafts, notes, interview transcripts, clippings, publications, and other materials, mostly related to the research and writing of In Our Own Hands, published in 1994. It also includes sets of original records dating from the 1940s to 1970s.
  - Topical materials
    - Era's [sic] of the ICC (Box 47)
    - Wolverine Eating Club (Box 47)
    - Housing/socialists (Box 47)
    - Book exchange and book stand (Socialist club) (Box 47)
    - Politics 1973 (Box 47)
    - Diversity (Box 47)
    - Vision (Box 47)
    - Soc. Life (Box 47)
    - Ownership and growth (Box 47)
    - Business (Box 47)
    - Women (Box 47)
      (includes interviews with Jean Fairfax and Marge Piercy)
    - Religion and the ICC (Box 47)
  - Materials by year
    - 1940s (Box 47)
    - 1940s articles and letters (Box 47)
    - 1940s board minutes (Box 47)
    - 1946 (Box 47)
    - 1947 (Box 47)
    - 1960s (Box 47)
    - 1970s (Box 47)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Notes, documents, and drafts (Box 47)
    - Pre-history materials (Box 47)
    - Various ICC histories, 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Michigan history (Box 48)
    - K. Pickerill notes 1943-1944 (Box 48)
    - Orr, Charles, early 1930s (Box 48)
    - History by decades (Box 48)
    - ICC historical notes and research (Box 48)
    - Oral histories (Box 48)
- House Records
  The material in the House Records series (1934-2010) document individual ICC houses and include a mixture of minutes, the constitution of the house, newsletters, photographs (most images, however, are found in the Audio-Visual series), and files relating to the history or administration of a house. The series is divided into 42 subseries; the first 39 correspond to the names of houses and are arranged alphabetically, from Bag-End to Zapata. materials in these subseries are arranged by document type: first minutes, then constitutions or rules, and other materials such as administrative, financial, or event records; house "history" files; or photographs. Following the subseries for the houses are materials for the Division Councils and Boarding Co-ops, including minutes and constitutions. The Multiple Houses subseries contains materials that relate to several houses, including sets of mixed or combined membership and financial records. The Legal and Financial Documents subseries includes materials relating to the legal purchase and ownership of the various houses. Within this subseries, materials are arranged by document type and then chronologically.
  - Bag-End
    - House minutes 1981-1982 (Box 14)
    - House constitution (Box 14)
    - House information (Box 14)
  - Black Elk
    - House minutes
      - September 1987-March 1988 (Box 14)
      - April 1988-September 1988 (Box 14)
      - October 1988-February 1989 (Box 14)
      - March 1989-May 1989 (Box 14)
      - September 1989-December 1989 (Box 14)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 14)
      - 1992-1995 (Box 14)
      - 2003-2006 (Box 14)
    - House constitution 1980-1995 (Box 14)
    - House history (Box 14)
  - Brandeis
    - House minutes 1962-1970, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - House constitutions (Box 14)
    - House work schedules 1941-1942 (Box 14)
    - Mixed materials (Box 14)
  - Bruce (Lenny Bruce) House
    - House Minutes
      - January 1976-October 1986 (Box 14)
      - November 1986-September 1987 (Box 14)
    - House Constitution 1984-1986 (Box 14)
    - House Records 1987-1988, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - House Committee Records
      - 1987-1988, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Newsletter The Beast, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Congress
    - House history (Box 14)
  - Debs
    - House Minutes
      - March 1967-May 1986 (Box 14)
      - 1990-2009 (Box 14)
    - House Constitution 1981-1995 (Box 14)
    - House history (Box 14)
  - Falstaff
    - House constitution (Box 14)
    - House welcome letter (Box 14)
  - Gregory
    - House minutes
      - 1995-1997 (Box 14)
      - 1998-2005 (Box 14)
      - 2006-2009 (Box 14)
      - 2010 (Box 14)
    - House Constitution July 1995 (Box 14)
    - House history (Box 14)
    - House acquisition and development (Box 34)
      - General materials 1995 (Box 34)
      - Zoning and city issues 1995-1996 (Box 34)
      - Plans and drawings 1995 (Box 34)
      - Feasibility information circa 1995 (Box 34)
      - Membership and start-up issues 1995 (Box 34)
      - Water bill issues 1995 (Box 34)
    - House namesake (Karl D. Gregory) biographical information 1995-1996 (Box 34)
    - House cast of characters (Box 34)
  - Kagawa
    - Address Change/Appeals/City Inspections 1990-1991 (Box 34)
    - House Documents (Development) and History 1990s, 4 folders (Box 34)
    - Conversion Plans 1994-1997 (Box 34)
    - House namesake (Toyohiko Kagawa) biographical information 1971-1990 (Box 34)
  - Karma
    - House minutes 1970-1971, 1977 (Box 34)
    - House information/correspondence 1979-1981 (Box 34)
  - King
    - House Minutes
      - June 1982-December 1989 (Box 34)
      - 1990-2000 (Box 34)
    - House Constitution
      - 1990-Present (Box 34)
    - House history (includes materials on Brandeis House) (Box 34)
  - Lester (Muriel Lester) House
    - House Minutes
      - March 1942-August 1947 (Box 34)
      - Fall 1947-February 1950 (Box 34)
      - January 1951-March 1953 (Box 34)
      - January 1954-February 1966 (Box 34)
      - October 1973-January 1979 (Box 34)
      - January 1979-September 1980 (Box 34)
      - May 1981-February 1988 (Box 34)
      - 1990-1997 (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
      - 1999 (summer) (Box 34)
      - 2002-2006 (Box 34)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 34)
    - House Constitution
      - 1952-1966 (Box 34)
    - Member Lists 1940-1990 (Box 34)
    - House history, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - "Memories of Lester Co-op" by Luther H. Buchele 1993 (Box 15)
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Lincoln
    - House minutes 1941-1943 (Box 15)
    - House information 1939, circa 1945 (Box 15)
    - House financial records 1941-1945 (Box 15)
  - Linder
    - House Minutes
      - September 1989-November 1989 (Box 15)
      - 1990-1995 (Box 15)
      - 1996-1999 (Box 15)
      - 2000-2009 (Box 15)
      - 2010 (Box 15)
    - House Constitution 1990 (Box 15)
    - House history (Box 15)
  - Luchtkasteel
    - House minutes 1970s (Box 15)
    - House constitution (Box 15)
  - Luther
    - House Minutes
      - November 1985-May 1986 (Box 15)
      - June 1986-January 1989 (Box 15)
      - 1994-2009 (Box 15)
      - 2010 (Box 15)
    - House Constitution
      - 1986-ca.2005 (Box 15)
    - House history
      - Residential lease and other materials 1971-1988 (Box 15)
      - News articles 1985-1986 (Box 15)
      - Acquisition materials 1986 (Box 15)
      - Mixed materials (Box 15)
  - Mark VIII/Joint/Tri-House
    - House Minutes
      - September 1957-June 1962 (Box 15)
      - September 1962-June 1972 (Box 15)
      - 1970 (Box 15)
      - May 1972-July 1973 (Box 15)
      - May 1973-May 1974 (Box 15)
      - June 1974-February 1975 (Box 15)
      - March 1975-February 1977 (Box 15)
      - March 1977-July 1978 (Box 15)
      - August 1978-March 1987 (Box 15)
      - April 1987-January 1988 (Box 15)
      - February 1988-October 1988 (Box 15)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 15)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 35)
      - 1998-2009 (Box 35)
    - House Constitution
      - August 1965-September 1971 (Box 35)
      - February 1974-1977 (Box 35)
      - 1977 (Box 35)
      - 1977- circa 2000 (Box 35)
    - Newsletter Abhishek, 1959 (Box 35)
    - House history
      - Financial schedules and plans 1956-1970 (Box 35)
      - Mixed 1969-2007 (Box 35)
        (includes photographs)
      - 1978 (Box 35)
  - Michigan
    - House Minutes
      - March 1941-December 1951 (Box 35)
      - January 1952-December 1953 (Box 35)
      - September 1954-December 1957 (Box 35)
      - January 1958-December 1963 (Box 35)
      - January 1964-November 1966 (Box 35)
      - February 1967-November 1967 (Box 35)
      - 1968-1983 (Box 35)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 35)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 35)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 35)
      - 1990-1994 (Box 35)
      - 1995-2004 (Box 35)
      - 2005-2009 (Box 35)
    - House Constitution 1946-1996 (Box 35)
    - House Records
      - 1934 (Box 35)
      - 1937 (Box 35)
      - 1938-1939, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - 1940-1941 (Box 35)
      - 1943 (Box 35)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 35)
      - 1948-1951 (Box 35)
      - 1972 (Box 35)
    - House history
      - Mixed 1940s, 1950s (Box 35)
      - Rehabilitation project bid 1978 (Box 35)
  - Minnie's
    - House Minutes
      - 1970-1983 (Box 16)
      - 1984-1989 (Box 16)
      - 1993-2009 (Box 16)
    - House Constitution 1980, 1987-1996 (Box 16)
    - House history (Box 16)
  - Nakamura
    - House Minutes
      - September 1948-February 1953 (Box 16)
      - February 1953-March 1957 (Box 16)
      - March 1957-December 1960 (Box 16)
      - February 1961-September 1965 (Box 16)
      - January 1966-December 1968 (Box 16)
      - January 1969-September 1970 (Box 16)
      - May 1971-October 1972 (Box 16)
      - March 1973-December 1974 (Box 16)
      - August 1978-October 1989 (Box 16)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 16)
      - 2006-2009 (Box 16)
      - 2010 (Box 16)
    - House Records
      - 1945-1948 (Box 16)
      - 1948-1955 (Box 16)
    - 50th anniversary materials 1997-1998 (Box 16)
    - House history, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - North Campus Co-ops
    - Building Oversight Committee minutes and related materials,1988-1990 (Box 16)
    - Standing rules revisions and other materials 1969-1981 (Box 16)
    - Constitution and standing rules 1978-1983, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Mixed administrative materials 1970-1984 (Box 16)
    - History (Box 16)
    - Other documents
      - Start-up/Planning Documents 1964-1970 (Box 16)
      - Memo from a former resident 1982 (Box 16)
      - Reorganization 1983-1985 (Box 16)
      - North Campus Restructuring 1984 (Box 16)
      - Maintenance Documents 1984-1987 (Box 16)
      - Management and decentralization ideas 1984-1990 (Box 16)
      - Proposed changes to North Campus Building Oversight Committee and ICC governance 1990 (Box 16)
      - Third Board of Directors representative ideas/responses 1992 (Box 16)
      - Proposed changes in governance for the ICC 1992 (Box 16)
      - North Campus Boarding Cooperative constitution (proposal failed) 1994 (Box 16)
      - Planning materials 1995 (Box 16)
      - Esher house ballot 1996 (Box 16)
      - Diversity graphs circa 1996 (Box 16)
      - Room payment rates materials 1992-1997 (Box 16)
  - O'Keeffe (Georgia O'Keeffe) House
    - House Minutes
      - September 1985-February 1986 (Box 36)
      - 1991-1994 (Box 36)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 36)
      - 1997 (Box 36)
      - 1998-2000 (Box 36)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 36)
      - 2006-2008 (Box 36)
    - House Constitution
      - 1980s, 2 folders (Box 36)
      - 1988 (Box 36)
      - 1994, 1996 (Box 36)
    - House Handbooks undated (Box 36)
    - Manual: Work Scheduler's Handbook 1984 (Box 36)
    - House history (Box 36)
  - Osterweil
    - House Minutes
      - September 1949-September 1959 (Box 36)
      - February 1960-December 1964 (Box 36)
      - January 1965-March 1988 (Box 36)
      - 1991-1997 (Box 36)
      - 2000-2009 (Box 36)
    - House Constitution 1955-2005 (Box 36)
    - House Records 1947-1971 (Box 36)
    - House administrative and financial materials 1950 (Box 36)
    - Invitations 1953 (Box 36)
    - 50th anniversary materials 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - House history
      - 1944-1996, 2 folders (Box 36)
      - 1946 (Box 36)
  - Owen
    - House Minutes
      - April 1947-July 1949 (Box 36)
      - 1950-1957 (Box 36)
      - 1954-1961 (Box 36)
      - January 1960-October 1962 (Box 36)
      - January 1963-December 1963 (Box 36)
      - January 1964-April 1964 (Box 36)
      - August 1964-October 1964 (Box 36)
      - November 1964-May 1965 (Box 36)
      - July 1965-January 1966 (Box 37)
      - January 1966-December 1966 (Box 37)
      - January 1967-December 1967 (Box 37)
      - January 1968-November 1968 (Box 37)
      - January 1969-December 1971 (Box 37)
      - Fall 1972 (Box 37)
      - January 1972-January 1976 (Box 37)
      - February 1976-November 1979 (Box 37)
      - August 1980-September 1985 (Box 37)
      - February 1986-1989 (Box 37)
      - 1993-2004 (Box 37)
      - 2010 (Box 37)
    - House Constitution
      - circa 1955 (Box 37)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 37)
      - 1970s (Box 37)
      - 1976 (Box 37)
      - 1986 (Box 37)
    - President's Manual materials (Box 37)
    - House administrative and financial materials 1950-1951 (Box 37)
    - Meeting notes October 1982 (Box 37)
    - 50th anniversary materials 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Mixed materials
      - 1950-1953 (Box 37)
      - circa 1955-1988 (Box 37)
    - House history, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Palmer
    - House history (Box 37)
  - Renaissance
    - House Minutes
      - September 1985-April 1986 (Box 37)
      - 1990-1995 (Box 37)
      - 1996-2005 (Box 37)
      - 2006 (Box 37)
      - 2007 (Box 37)
      - 2008 (Box 37)
    - House Constitution
      - 1985-1990 (Box 37)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 37)
    - Expulsion proceedings 1995 (Box 37)
  - Rochdale
    - Correspondence and other materials 1939-1945 (Box 37)
    - House summarized profit and loss statements 1939-1940 (Box 37)
    - House financial records 1939-1940 (Box 37)
    - House monthly financial statements 1940-1941 (Box 37)
    - House summarized profit and loss statements 1941 (Box 37)
    - House balance sheets and statements of members 1940-1941 (Box 37)
    - House history (Box 37)
  - Russell
    - House correspondence and minutes 1970 (Box 37)
    - House information (Box 37)
    - House work schedules circa 1973 (Box 37)
  - Ruths'
    - House Minutes
      - 1993-1999 (Box 17)
      - 2000-2008 (Box 17)
      - 2010 (Box 17)
    - House constitution
      - Cat Policy undated (Box 17)
    - House history (Box 17)
  - Sinclair (John Sinclair) House
    - House minutes
      - 1970-1974 (bound) (Box 17)
      - 1970 (Box 17)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 17)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 17)
      - 1980-1983 (Box 17)
    - House constitution
      - 1970, 1978 (Box 17)
      - 1981 (Box 17)
    - House correspondence and other materials (Box 17)
  - Stalker
    - House history 1986 (Box 17)
  - Stevens (A.K. Stevens) House
    - House Minutes
      - February 1949-March 1965 (Box 17)
      - July 1971-December 1975 (Box 17)
      - January 1976-December 1979 (Box 17)
      - February 1980-December 1984 (Box 17)
      - January 1985-September 1987 (Box 17)
      - January 1988-1989 (Box 17)
      - January 1990-December 1990 (Box 17)
      - January 1991-March 1993 (Box 17)
      - April 1993-November 1994 (Box 17)
      - May 1995-September 1998 (Box 17)
      - January 1999-July 2001 (Box 17)
    - House Constitution
      (also includes "Thayer Street House")
      - 1954-1996 (Box 17)
    - House Records
      - 1943-1949 (Box 17)
      - 1950-1967 (Box 17)
    - Financial records 1946 (Box 17)
    - House History
      - 1943-1993 (Box 17)
      - 1978-2004 (Box 17)